# JIAN LEAO

# **BlockChain Frontend Developer**

**\** +1-131-807-8134

@ jianleao@gmail.com

https://www.github.com/superbluestar

Singapore, SG

## **SUMMARY**

Passionate Blockchain front-end web&mobile developer with 5+ years of experience coding websites that convert in e-commerce. I am a front-end developer with strong time-management skills, collaborative team working abilities, problem-solving expertise, passion for my work, and the ability to quickly understand new concepts and technologies.

# **EXPERIENCE**

12/2021 - 03/2023

# Senior Frontend Developer

Singapore, SG

#### **Agile Lab**

Web, Mobile & Blockchain Development with Agile Methodology. Specialist in Ruby on Rails, React, Node JS. We build MVPs for Startups and Customised Systems.

- · Update Business Mobile App "Axpert" company main project.
- Participated in the development of desktop/mobile wallet using React, React Native, Flutter and Electron
- Participated in smart contract development and React Native mobile app development.
- Successfully published private block-chain using EOS.

#### 07/2020 - 10/2021

#### Mobile Developer

Singapore, SG

#### **Adaptis GmbH**

Adaptis is a global technical agency with locations in Switzerland, Australia, Singapore, and Vietnam.

- · Increased by 35% the reach of users to the platform, over the installation of the web platform in mobile devices
- · Developed React Native iOS, Android and Web applications for FullStack clients
- Overhauled the automated test framework for the web services, leading to about 90% reduction in debugging and issue resolution time
- Started as the first web developer, ultimately growing to a team of 8

## 03/2018 - 06/2020

## Junior Web Developer

Singapore, SG

#### Zencloud

Zencloud Technology discuss the latest trends and powerful software that business in Singapore can implement in their company operation to improve efficiency and productivity.

- · Converted a Figma design into HTML pages using React, HTML, CSS while closely working with designers.
- Mobilized cross-platform testing on 4 different web browsers and 3 standalone applications in web and cloud base
- Contributed to the development of over 10 web and mobile applications
- Worked in a team of 6 people for several kind of front-end task

### **EDUCATION**

04/2013 - 10/2017

Dover, SG

BSc in Computer Engineering

The Singapore Institute of Technology

GPA 3.75 / 4.0

#### **TECH STACK**

TypeScript	React Nex	t.js Gatsby.js	Node.js	Ethers	s.js Next.	s W	leb3.js	React Native	Flutter
BlockChain	Smart Contrac	t Ethereum	Solidity	EOS	GraphQL	Git	Github		

Powered by Enhancy